Guide to the Martin Sedlazek NASA Collection, 1953-1999
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
Martin Sedlazek NASA collection
1953-1999
C0293
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
6.0 linear feet (20 boxes)
The Martin Sedlazek NASA Collection includes educational and informational reports, white papers, memos, and press information from Martin Sedlazek's career in the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), including information on Saturn V, Apollo missions, and the Space Station.
National Aeronautics and Space Administration.
Sedlazek, Martin
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Martin Sedlazek on October 24, 2016.
Biographical Information
Martin F. Sedlazek held a 30-year tenure with the National Aeronautical and Space Administration (NASA) in both technical and administrative management positions that spanned the organization - from Headquarters in program policy-type positions (12 years) to the Field Center in hardware project management assignments (18 years). These included association with both manned and unmanned programs, such as Apollo and the Space Station, as well as the Delta Launch Vehicle and the PAM Project (a commercially developed upper stage used with the NASA shuttle and expendable launch vehicles to place satellites into geosynchronous orbit), respectively.
Coming to NASA with an electrical engineering background, Sedlazek contributed to many projects and efforts throughout his career there, and held responsibilities such as user integration, managing technical oversight of the PAM Project, managing of the resource elements of the Delta Launch Vehicle, and technical program control experience with the Apollo program. He also acted as Director of Resources Management in the Office of Applications for 6 years, and was responsible for R&D budget planning and execution, including OMB and Congressional budget process implementation, policy development, and administrative and personnel management. During this time as Director of Resources Management he also implemented a budget control system that made more effective use of under-utilized research funds.
Scope and Content
The Martin Sedlazek NASA Collection includes materials spanning from Sedlazek's 30-year career in the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA). The collection consists of educational and informational reports, pamphlets, and booklets, white papers, memos, press information, photographs, and other documents. Most of the focus of the collections centers on materials pertaining to the Space Shuttle, the Space Station, Skylab, Saturn V, the Flight Telerobotic Servicer, and other documents such as briefings, letters, inter-administration and inter-department memoranda and reports, information on astronauts, international agreements, as well as plans and chronologies of NASA. The bulk of the collection originates from the mid 1960s through the 1970s.
Arrangement
This collection was arranged in the original order it was received by the donor, with the exception of numbered materials arranged in numerical order when necessary.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
National Aeronautics and Space Administration.
Subjects:
Project Apollo (U.S.); Saturn V (Satellite); Skylab Program; Space Station Program (U.S.)
Contents List
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Space Technology, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Communications and Navigation, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Earth Observations, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Earth and Ocean Physics, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Materials Processing and Space Manufacturing, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Executive Summaries, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - High Energy Astrophysics, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Putting Space to Work - Annual Report of the NASA Office of Applications, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Putting Space to Work - Annual Report of the NASA Office of Applications, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Comet Kohoutek - A Teacher's Guide with Student Activities by Robert D. Chapman, Ph. D., September 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NASA Space Station - GSFC Management Review by Ronald K. Browning, June 9, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Space Station - Presentation to the President's National Commission On Space by Philip E. Culbertson - Associate Administrator Office of Space Station, May 15, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Practical Applications of a Space Station, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Civilian Space Stations and the U.S. Future in Space, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Economic Analysis of the Space Shuttle System by Klaus P. Heiss and Oskar Morgenstern, January 3, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Design Guidelines for Robotic Serviceable Instruments - Preliminary Guidelines Document, August 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Goddard's Management Plan For Space Station Freedom - Review Copy, February 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Space Shuttle Pamphlet, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- U.S. Manned Space Flight - The Manned Flight Program - The Astronauts, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Manned Space Flight Pamphlet, October 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- On the Moon with Apollo 15 - A Guidebook to Hadley Rille and the Apennine Mountains by Gene Simmons, June 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Planetary Program Review, July 11, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Exploration of the Solar System, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- New Horizons, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Skylab Program - Technical Summary Handbook, February 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Astronomy, May 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Atmospheric and Space Physics, May 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Solar Physics, May 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Final Report of the Space Shuttle Payload Planning Working Groups - Life Sciences, May 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Space Shuttle EVA (Extravehicular Activity) Opportunities, circa 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- United States Activities in Spacecraft Oceanography, October 1, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Skylab, Outpost on the Frontier of Space by Thomas Y. Canby, October 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- The NASA Program - A Forecast of the 70's, March 1, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- U.S. Manned Space Flight - The Manned Flight Program - The Astronauts, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Skylab Pamphlet/Poster, June 1, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Apollo Mission Briefs - Revision 12, January 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Ecological Surveys From Space, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Space - A Resource for Earth - An AIAA (American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics), April 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Aviation Week and Space Technology Magazine, October 17, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- IEEE (The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers) Spectrum Magazine, October 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Spacelab Users Guide, November 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Apollo 14 - Preliminary Science Report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Space Shuttle - Program Requirements Document - Level 1, April 21, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Saturn Program - Schedules and Status Summary, March 2, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Advanced Study/New Start Planning - Briefing to Dr. Naugle, November 16, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- National Aeronautics and Space Administration - Chronological History, 1959 - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Pre-Mars Orbit Insertion and Landing - Mission Operation Report, June 9, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Master Data Processor Pamphlet, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- TRW telecommunications - Satellites Pamphlet, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Astronautics and Aeronautics Magazine, April 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- For the Benefit of All Mankind Informational Report with Letter From Donald V. Beall Attached, circa 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Satellite Pamphlets and Business Card of Draper Hill, Editorial Cartoonist, circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Director's Program Review - Materials Research, March 17, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Skylab and the Sun, July 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Communications Satellites - Fairchild Industries, circa 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Apollo 17 Pamphlet, circa 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- NASA Activities Pamphlet - 15th Anniversary, 1958-1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- NASA Pocket Statistics - History (Published Semi-Annually), July 1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Earth Observatory Satellite - System Definition Study - Executive Summary, November 1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- World Weather Program - Plan for Fiscal Year, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- NASA Facts - Space Shuttle Fold Out Informational Poster, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Skylab Experiments - Volume 5 - Astronomy and Space Physics, November 27, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Photography From Space to Help Solve Problems on Earth, circa 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Dirigibles: Naval Vehicles for Tomorrow, June 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Skylab Experiments - Volume 7 - Living and Working in Space, November 27, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Skylab Experiments - Volume 6 - Mechanics, November 27, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- America In Space - The First Decade - Man in Space by David A. Anderton, October 1, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Aviation Week and Space Technology Magazine, July 2, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- The Post-Apollo Space Program Directions for the Future, September 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- America's Next Decade in Space - A Report for the Space Task Group, September 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- The Next Decade in Space, March 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- The Space Applications Program Appendices, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Earth and Ocean Physics Applications Program - Volume I Executive Summary, September 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Earth and Ocean Physics Applications Program - Volume II Rationale and Program Plans, September 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Nimbus - The Growth Satellite Informational Report, circa 1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Apollo Lunar Exploration by G.M. Low and L.R. Scherer, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- United States Activities in Spacecraft Oceanography, October 1, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Space Station: Key to the Future, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- America in Space - The First Decade - Aeronautics by David A. Anderton, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- NASA Photograph of Astronaut Alan B. Shepard Jr., Commander of Apollo 14 Mission, February 15, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- NASA Photograph - Gemini VI Space Photography by Astronauts Schirra and Stafford - Clouds over Southeast Indian Ocean, December 16, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NASA Photograph - Gemini XI Space Photography by Astronauts Conrad and Gordan -Ethiopia, Somali, French Somaliland, Saudi Arabia, Yemen, South Arabia, Red Sea, Gulf of Aden, September 12-15, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Apollo 7 Space Photography - Persian Gulf Coastal Area of Iran, Qushm Island, November 2, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NASA Facts - Observing Earth from Skylab, circa 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- NASA Facts - Why Survey from Space?, circa 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- NASA Facts - The Spectrum - There's More Than Meets the Eye - Informational Pamphlet/Poster, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Comparisons - First Wright Flight and Apollo II - Saturn 5 Flight, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Statement of Donald P. Hearth - Planetary Programs - The Results of Mariners 6 and 7 and Their Implications - Includes Photos of Mariner VII, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- NASA - Group of Photographs of Mariner 6, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Space Station: Key to the Future, circa 1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Titan III - Building Blocks to Space, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Speech by George M. Low, Acting NASA Administrator, November 19, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Our Future in Space: A Challenge in Leadership - Luncheon Speech by George M. Low, October 19, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- The Impact of Man and His Environment on the Space Program by George M. Low, October 22, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- International Aspects of Our Space Program by George M. Low, January 26, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Statement of Representative Bob Casey, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Science and Scientists: Obligations and Opportunities by Philip Handler, President, National Academy of Sciences, October 21, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- "A Time for Decision" by Edgar M. Cartright, October 28, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Aerospace Management - NASA's Major Challenges For the Seventies, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Earth Observations Program Review, November 4-5, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- America in Space - The First Decade - Exploring the Moon and Planets by William R. Corliss, October 1, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- NASA Facilities Data, October 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- The Apollo Spacecraft - A Chronology - Volume I, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Space Science and Applications, October 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Astronomy Programs Review, June 2-3, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Communications Programs Review, January 21, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- NASA Facts - Educational Publication - Mars as a Member of the Solar System, December 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Memorandum on Study of Aerospace Management Techniques from D. J. Harnett, February 1, 1972 - Attached to Aerospace Management Techniques: Commercial and Governmental Applications by J. Gordon Milliken and Edward J. Morrison, November 1971, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Aboard the Space Shuttle Educational Pamphlet, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Apollo 14: Science at Fra Mauro by Walter Froehlich, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- McDonnell Douglas Payload Assist Module (PAM) - Educational Materials in Folder, November 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Office of Manned Space Flight - Apollo Program - Apollo Configuration Management Manual, May 18, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Office of Manned Space Flight - Apollo Program - NASA Apollo Program Management - Volume I, December 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Note from James C. Fletcher to NASA Employees, August 14, 1986, Attached to Report to the President - Actions to Implement the Recommendation of the Presidential Commission on the Space Shuttle Challenger Accident - Executive Summary, July 14, 1986, August 14, 1986 and July 14, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Information on Earth-Moon Transits, circa 1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Aviation Week and Space Technology Magazine, June 20, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Saturn V Flight Manual - SA 506, February 25, 1969, Changed June 10, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Mercury Project Summary Including Results of the Fourth Manned Orbital Flight, May 15-16, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Missiles and Rockets - The Weekly of Space Systems Engineering Pamphlet, August 13, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Fairchild Stratos - Spacecraft Systems Engineering Pamphlet, Highlighting the New Team for Space Development, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Letter from T.J. Vincent to ill Sneed Concerning "Fairplan" Manual, October 12, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Saturn Illustrated Chronology - Saturn's First Eight Years, April 1957 - April 1965, May 15, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Grumman Aircraft Engineering Corporation - Lunar Module Subsystem Assembly and Installations, December 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Saturn V - Component Qualification Test Program - Status Analysis Monthly Report, March 8, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Saturn V Configuration Management Implementation Program for Marshall Space Flight Center, July 27, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Note on Distribution of Baseline Configuration Document from Charles N. Crews, January 15, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Baseline Configuration Document - Space Station Program Office, January 15, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Saturn V Master Test Plan, October 20, 1965, June 1, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Management Procedures In Computer Programming For Apollo - Interim Report, November 30, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Saturn V Program Schedules, Status and Analysis, March 2, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Saturn V - Pert Status and Project Trends - Program Control Office, July 8, 966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- The President's Plan for Space - A Partnership for Progress - Statement for Press Briefing from James M. Beggs, NASA Administrator, January 26, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Letter to James "Jim" M. Beggs from The Secretary of Defense, January 16, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Defense Daily - Space Station Science Adviser Wants Science Heeded, January 16, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- NASA News - Space Station Proposals Sought, September 14, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- NASA News - Four NASA Centers Assigned Space Station Studies, June 28, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Data Requirements for the Payload Data Package Annex - Payload Integration Plan Annex No. 1, July 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Letter to William R. Graham from the House of Representatives Committee on Appropriations, January 14, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Soviet Salyut 8 Space Station Diagram, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Space Station Program Concerns by Gordon Fullerton, June 20, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Management Review of Space Station Program - General Sam Phillips, June 26, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Space Station Management: An Analysis of Work Package Options, October 3, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Space Station Presentation to Mr. James Beggs Administrator, February 7, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Office of Space Station FY 1986 Budget Recommendation Administrator's Review, August 22, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Space Station Program Planning Status - Presentation to NASA Policy Review Committee, May 15, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Flight Telerobotic Servicer to User Interface Control Document, July 10, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Proposed Change Request for Collision Avoidance, July 27, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Space Station Freedom Robotic Systems Integration Standards, July 15, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Space Station Work Package - 3 Prime Contractor Request for Proposal Review, November 4, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Group of Materials - Including Photographs and Informational Materials - on Terra, NASA's Earth Observing System, circa 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Space Station Program History: 1981 - 1987, February 12, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Briefing to Dr. James C. Fletcher, Administrator - Summary Results of the Space Station Operations Task Force, May 1, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Space Station Reference Configuration - Systems Engineering and Integration Space Station Program Office Cover, August 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Space Station - The Next Logical Step, circa 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 1 - Weather and Climate, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 2 - Uses of Communications, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 3 - Land Use Planning, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 4 - Agriculture, Forest, and Range, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 5 - Inland Water Resources, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 6 - Extractable Resource, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 7 - Environmental Quality, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 8 - Marine and Maritime Uses, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 9 - Materials Processing in Space, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 10 - Institutional Arrangements, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 11 - Costs and Benefits, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 12 - Space Transportation, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 13 - Information Services and Information Processing, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems - Supporting Paper 14 - Technology, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Two Over Mars - Mariner VI and Mariner VII, February - August 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Federal Research and Development for Satellite Communications, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Manual for the Preparation of Project Status Review (PSR) Report and Monthly Status Review (MSR) Report - Revision 1, November 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Practical Applications of Space Systems, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 1 Introduction and Summary - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 2 Mission Description Document - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 3 System Requirements and Characteristics - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 4 Advanced Development Program - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Space Station Program Description Document - Book 6 System Operations - Prepared By The: Space Station Task Force, March 1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Four Overhead Projector Slides - Diagrams, circa 1985? (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Note from Martin Sedlazek Concerning and Attached to Document of Comments on Level A Program Requirements Documents, August 30, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Advance Copy of Interim Baseline Decisions, August 17, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Space Station Program - Program Requirements Document, April 5, 1984 - Attached to Note Concerning Its Distribution from Philip E. Culbertson, June 25, 1984, April 5, 1984 and June 25, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Space Station Program - Program Requirements Document, April 5, 1984 - Attached to Note on Its Distribution from John D. Hodge, April 6, 1984, April 5 - 6, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Space Station Program Requirements Document, August 15, 1984, Attached to Note on Distribution of Document, August 15, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Rephased Program Capability (RPC) Utilization Assessment, September 6, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Initial OSSA Reactions to the Space Station Rephasing, September 19, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Space Station Freedom External Maintenance, July 20, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Flight Telerobotic Servicer (FTS) - Configuration/Performance Requirements, circa 1985? (Box 11, Folder 6)
- FTS - Flight Telerobotic Servicer - Expanding U.S. Robotic Technologies Informational Report, circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Space Station Program Systems Engineering and Integration - RUR-2 Results and Summary, November 1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Level A/B Program Review - Space Station Development Program Cost Estimate, August 23, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Space Station FY 1985 Budget Hearing - Space Science and Applications Subcommittee - U.S. House of Representatives - Backup Data, February 2, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Space Station Presentation to the NASA Advisory Council, July 18, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Polar Orbiting Platform System Concept Review, March 15, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- User Accommodation Assessment "SRR Results", May 5, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Critical Evaluation Task Force Impacts - Presented to SSCB, October 3, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Critical Evaluation Task Force - Report to the NASA Executive Technical Committee, September 8, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)